<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news</id>
    <title>UNC Chapel Hill AAUP</title>
    <updated>2021-06-21T14:50:25.597Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>UNC-CH AAUP</name>
        <email>info@unc-ch-aaup.org</email>
        <uri>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/feed.atom"/>
    <subtitle>UNC Chapel Hill chapter of the American Association of University Professors</subtitle>
    <logo>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/favicon-32x32.png</logo>
    <icon>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statement by AAUP national leadership and commentaries by chapter members on Nikole Hannah-Jones’s appointment]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-06-04</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-06-04"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On May 20, the  University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill (UNC-CH) chapter of the American Association of University Professors (AAUP) posted a <a href="/assets/unc-nikole-hannah-jones-tenure-june-21.pdf">statement condemning the UNC-CH Board of Trustees (BOT) for failing to award tenure to Nikole Hannah-Jones</a> (statement updated June 21, 2021 to clarify that the the BOT did not reject Hannah-Jones’s tenure recommendation but failed to act on it).</p>
<p>Now the national leadership of the AAUP has posted a <a href="https://www.aaup.org/news/statement-unc-board-and-nikole-hannah-jones">statement on the UNC Board and Nikole Hannah-Jones</a>, calling on the Board “to immediately reverse its mistaken move to withhold tenure and accept the faculty&#39;s recommendation that Nikole Hannah-Jones be appointed to the Knight chair with tenure.”</p>
<p>UNC-CH AAUP chapter member Hassan Melehy has written a commentary for the Academe Blog on <a href="https://academeblog.org/2021/06/03/the-right-wing-renewal-of-higher-education-in-north-carolina/">“The Right-Wing ‘Renewal’ of Higher Education in North Carolina</a> pointing out that the Board’s failure is just the latest example of the influence over the UNC System Board of Governors and the UNC–CH BOT exercised by conservative activist groups like the Raleigh-based James G. Martin Center for Academic Renewal.</p>
<p>At Slate, UNC-CH professor Alice Marwick and UNC-CH professor and UNC-CH AAUP chapter member Daniel Kreiss have written an article on <a href="https://slate.com/technology/2021/06/nikole-hannah-jones-unc-1619-project-disinformation-campaign.html"> “The Conservative Disinformation Campaign Against Nikole Hannah-Jones”</a> that puts the situation at UNC-CH in the broader context of “a long-term conservative battle against public higher education and the teaching of American racial history.”</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNC-CH AAUP statement on Nikole Hannah-Jones’s appointment]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-05-20</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-05-20"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill’s Board of Trustees (BOT), <a href="http://www.ncpolicywatch.com/2021/05/19/pw-special-report-after-conservative-criticism-unc-backs-down-from-offering-acclaimed-journalist-a-tenured-position/">apparently bowing to pressure from the UNC System’s Board of Governors (BOG)</a>, has <s>rejected</s> <a href="https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/education/article251527603.html">failed to act on a tenure recommendation</a> that had the full support of UNC-Chapel Hill Hussman School of Journalism and Media’s <a href="https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/education/article250945664.html">faculty and Dean and of UNC-CH’s Chancellor</a>. By blocking Nikole Hannah-Jones’s appointment with tenure, the BOT and BOG have once again engaged in administrative overreach at UNC-Chapel Hill and violated the rules of faculty governance and academic freedom.</p>
<p>The Chapel Hill chapter of the American Association of University Professors (AAUP) objects in the strongest possible terms to this latest egregious attack on the core principles of <a href="https://www.aaup.org/our-work/protecting-academic-freedom">academic freedom</a> and <a href="https://www.aaup.org/our-programs/shared-governance">shared governance</a>. We join <a href="https://hussmanfaculty.medium.com/stunned-unc-hussman-schfaculty-statement-on-nikole-hannah-jones-6333c5f5d072">the Hussman School faculty</a> in demanding that the BOT immediately <s>reinstate</s> approve Hannah-Jones’s <s>original</s> appointment with tenure.</p>
<p>All UNC system and campus administrators must respect the faculty&#39;s central role in hiring and tenuring our colleagues and defining educational programming.</p>
<p>See the full <a href="/assets/unc-nikole-hannah-jones-tenure-june-21.pdf">UNC-CH AAUP statement on <s>the revoking of</s> Nikole Hannah-Jones’s appointment <s>with tenure</s></a> (statement updated June 21, 2021 to clarify that the the BOT did not reject Hannah-Jones’s tenure recommendation but failed to act on it).</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNC-CH AAUP statement on UNC chancellor searches]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-03-19</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-03-19"/>
        <updated>2021-03-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The UNC-Chapel Hill chapter of the American Association of University Professors (AAUP) is opposed to the current policy of allowing the UNC System President to name a finalist candidate for chancellor searches at UNC campuses.</p>
<p>The Board of Governors’ recent <a href="https://www.dailytarheel.com/article/2021/03/university-fsu-chancellor-controversy">appointment of Darrell Allison as Chancellor at Fayetteville State University</a>—after a normal search had created an initial list of finalists that did not include him—demonstrates that the current system is in violation of the AAUP’s principles of shared campus governance.</p>
<p>See the full <a href="/assets/unc-chancellor-searches-march-21.pdf">UNC-CH AAUP statement on UNC chancellor searches</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concerns about chancellor-elect at Fayetteville State / State AAUP meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-03-11</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-03-11"/>
        <updated>2021-03-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The AAUP national office has sent a <a href="/assets/aaup-letter-to-chair-augustine-3-9-21.pdf">letter of concern</a> to the chair of the Board of Trustees at Fayetteville State University regarding <a href="https://www.faystatefaculty.com/post/chancellor-selection-news-commentary-round-up">their recent selection of Mr. Darrell Allison as chancellor</a>. The faculty senate at Fayetteville State has passed a resolution urging the board to rescind the offer on the grounds that Mr. Allison “lacks the requisite academic experience necessary to serve as the leader of an academic institution.” See also this <a href="http://www.ncpolicywatch.com/2021/02/24/pw-special-report-how-did-darrell-allison-cut-in-line-to-become-the-new-chancellor-at-fayetteville-state-its-a-secret/">special report at NC Policy Watch</a>. It appears that the UNC System is once again subordinating the principles of shared governance.</p>
<p>The state AAUP meeting will be held this <strong>Saturday, March 13, from 1 to 3PM</strong> via Zoom.</p>
<p>The meeting’s agenda will be to discuss how shared governance and academic freedom have fared at different North Carolina institutions during COVID. The plan is to have members of each institution represented in the state conference briefly address the following questions, which relate to issues of institutional governance during the pandemic:</p>
<ol>
<li><p>How would you characterize the decision to change course delivery methods in response to the COVID-19 pandemic?</p>
</li>
<li><p>How would you characterize decisions to reopen the campus during the COVID-19 pandemic?</p>
</li>
<li><p>How would you characterize budget decisions in response to the COVID-19 pandemic?</p>
</li>
<li><p>In general, how influential has faculty participation been during the COVID-19 pandemic, and to what degree has faculty participation changed since the COVID-19 pandemic?</p>
</li>
<li><p>Since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic, have academic programs, majors, or minors been eliminated, or have no programs been eliminated?</p>
</li>
<li><p>Since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic, has the administration or board declared a financial exigency or fiscal emergency, or has there been no such declaration? Have there been terminations of faculty appointments, including faculty layoffs, or have there been no such terminations?</p>
</li>
<li><p>Since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic, has the administration or board unilaterally declared existing institutional regulations, such as sections of the faculty handbook, as no longer in force?</p>
</li>
<li><p>Have faculty at your institution faced any academic freedom issues related to the COVID-19 pandemic?</p>
</li>
<li><p>What are other current concerns faculty have at your institution?</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>If you are interested in attending, please contact Michael Behrent at <a href="mailto:&#109;&#105;&#99;&#104;&#x61;&#x65;&#108;&#99;&#x62;&#x65;&#104;&#x72;&#x65;&#x6e;&#x74;&#x40;&#x67;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#x6c;&#46;&#x63;&#111;&#109;">&#109;&#105;&#99;&#104;&#x61;&#x65;&#108;&#99;&#x62;&#x65;&#104;&#x72;&#x65;&#x6e;&#x74;&#x40;&#x67;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#x6c;&#46;&#x63;&#111;&#109;</a> to request the Zoom link. It will be made available to any AAUP member or faculty member who requests it.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March chapter meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-02-25</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-02-25"/>
        <updated>2021-02-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our next chapter meeting will be <strong>Friday, March 5, from noon to 1:30pm EST</strong>.</p>
<p>The meeting link and agenda will be posted next week. If you would like to suggest an agenda item, please contact one of the officers by Monday, March 1. </p>
<p>In the meantime, here are some recent news items of interest:</p>
<ol>
<li><p><a href="https://www.dailytarheel.com/article/2021/02/university-aaup-statement">Daily Tar Heel article</a> about our chapter&#39;s <a href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/unc-admin-breaches-of-trust">statement calling for the Chancellor to resign</a></p>
</li>
<li><p><a href="https://www.wunc.org/post/some-unc-chapel-hill-professors-call-chancellor-guskiewicz-resign">WUNC story about the statement</a></p>
</li>
<li><p><a href="https://www.dailytarheel.com/article/2021/02/opinion-guskiewicz-faculty-letter">Daily Tar Heel letter to the editor in response to the February 19 Faculty Council meeting</a></p>
</li>
<li><p><a href="https://www.dailytarheel.com/article/2021/02/opinion-unc-reinvest-oped">Daily Tar Heel op-ed by UNC Reinvest</a>, a group whose goals are aligned with the budget recommendations of <a href="https://www.anotheruncispossible.org">Another UNC is Possible</a></p>
</li>
<li><p><a href="https://www.dailytarheel.com/article/2021/02/another-unc-is-possible">Daily Tar Heel article about Another UNC is Possible</a></p>
</li>
<li><p><a href="https://www.aaup.org/report/statement-government-colleges-and-universities">Statement on Government of Colleges and Universities</a> from the the AAUP National office</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Please invite any interested colleagues. Our meetings are open to all UNC instructors, and you need not be an AAUP member to attend chapter meetings.</p>
<p>Karen Booth <a href="mailto:&#107;&#97;&#x72;&#x65;&#x6e;&#109;&#x62;&#x6f;&#111;&#116;&#x68;&#x40;&#x67;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#x6c;&#46;&#x63;&#x6f;&#x6d;">&#107;&#97;&#x72;&#x65;&#x6e;&#109;&#x62;&#x6f;&#111;&#116;&#x68;&#x40;&#x67;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#x6c;&#46;&#x63;&#x6f;&#x6d;</a></p>
<p>Michael Palm  <a href="mailto:&#x6d;&#119;&#x70;&#97;&#108;&#x6d;&#64;&#x67;&#109;&#x61;&#105;&#x6c;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#109;">&#x6d;&#119;&#x70;&#97;&#108;&#x6d;&#64;&#x67;&#109;&#x61;&#105;&#x6c;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#109;</a></p>
<p>Jay Smith  <a href="mailto:&#106;&#97;&#121;&#x73;&#109;&#105;&#x74;&#104;&#55;&#49;&#x31;&#x40;&#x67;&#x6d;&#97;&#x69;&#108;&#46;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;">&#106;&#97;&#121;&#x73;&#109;&#105;&#x74;&#104;&#55;&#49;&#x31;&#x40;&#x67;&#x6d;&#97;&#x69;&#108;&#46;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNC-CH AAUP statement on UNC administrators' serial breaches of trust]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-02-11</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-02-11"/>
        <updated>2021-02-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The serial dishonesty displayed by the UNC-Chapel Hill chancellor and his associates regarding the most sensitive and important matters confronting the University in recent years has eroded our confidence in UNC&#39;s leadership. The members of the UNC-Chapel Hill Chapter of the American Association of University Professors (AAUP) urge Chancellor Guskiewicz, and others who have contributed to UNC’s pattern of institutional dishonesty, to step down.</p>
<p>See the full <a href="/unc-admin-breaches-of-trust">UNC-CH AAUP statement on UNC administrators&#39; serial breaches of trust</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[February chapter meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-02-01</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2021-02-01"/>
        <updated>2021-02-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our next chapter meeting will be this Friday, February 5, from noon to 1:30pm EST. </p>
<p>Agenda:</p>
<ol>
<li>Spring Semester / reopening: new and ongoing concerns - 20 minutes </li>
<li>Budget - <a href="https://www.anotheruncispossible.org">AUNCiP</a>, <a href="https://pulse.ncpolicywatch.org/2021/01/26/unc-chapel-hill-halts-diversity-hiring-program-due-to-budget-concerns/">VITAE “pause”</a>, other updates and strategies - 20 minutes </li>
<li>Faculty Governance - increasing democracy and representation - 20 minutes </li>
<li>Chapter officers - proposal to extend terms a year, hold elections Fall &#39;21 - 5 minutes </li>
<li>Other issues and concerns, open discussion until 1:30</li>
</ol>
<p>Zoom link: <a href="https://us02web.zoom.us/j/88268257314">https://us02web.zoom.us/j/88268257314</a></p>
<p>Meeting ID: 882 6825 7314</p>
<p>For the Zoom passcode, please email <a href="mailto:&#105;&#110;&#102;&#x6f;&#64;&#117;&#x6e;&#99;&#x2d;&#99;&#104;&#x2d;&#x61;&#97;&#x75;&#112;&#46;&#111;&#114;&#x67;">&#105;&#110;&#102;&#x6f;&#64;&#117;&#x6e;&#99;&#x2d;&#99;&#104;&#x2d;&#x61;&#97;&#x75;&#112;&#46;&#111;&#114;&#x67;</a> or DM <a href="https://twitter.com/unc_ch_aaup">@unc_ch_aaup</a>, or contact one of the officers below.</p>
<p>Please invite any interested colleagues. UNC instructors need not be AAUP members to attend chapter meetings.</p>
<p>Karen Booth <a href="mailto:&#107;&#97;&#x72;&#x65;&#110;&#109;&#x62;&#111;&#111;&#116;&#x68;&#x40;&#103;&#109;&#x61;&#105;&#108;&#46;&#x63;&#111;&#x6d;">&#107;&#97;&#x72;&#x65;&#110;&#109;&#x62;&#111;&#111;&#116;&#x68;&#x40;&#103;&#109;&#x61;&#105;&#108;&#46;&#x63;&#111;&#x6d;</a></p>
<p>Michael Palm  <a href="mailto:&#109;&#x77;&#x70;&#x61;&#108;&#x6d;&#64;&#103;&#x6d;&#x61;&#x69;&#x6c;&#x2e;&#99;&#x6f;&#109;">&#109;&#x77;&#x70;&#x61;&#108;&#x6d;&#64;&#103;&#x6d;&#x61;&#x69;&#x6c;&#x2e;&#99;&#x6f;&#109;</a></p>
<p>Jay Smith  <a href="mailto:&#106;&#97;&#x79;&#115;&#109;&#x69;&#x74;&#104;&#55;&#49;&#49;&#64;&#103;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#x6c;&#x2e;&#x63;&#111;&#x6d;">&#106;&#97;&#x79;&#115;&#109;&#x69;&#x74;&#104;&#55;&#49;&#49;&#64;&#103;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#x6c;&#x2e;&#x63;&#111;&#x6d;</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open meeting regarding Spring semester - Friday 10/30 at noon]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2020-10-27</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2020-10-27"/>
        <updated>2020-10-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As many of our departments are scheduling next semester&#39;s courses, and
crucial decisions for Spring are being made, the UNC-CH chapter of the
AAUP invites all UNC students, employees, and community members to an
open meeting on <strong>Friday, Oct. 30th from Noon - 1:30pm EDT</strong>.</p>
<p><a href="https://unc.zoom.us/j/96570533947?pwd=WTFSOUxZUTgzNjE1emxHOC9DZklKQT09">https://unc.zoom.us/j/96570533947?pwd=WTFSOUxZUTgzNjE1emxHOC9DZklKQT09</a></p>
<p>UNC&#39;s plan to reopen campuses for the start of the Fall semester was
fundamentally flawed and doomed to fail. Across the U.S., young adults
ages 18 to 22 saw a 55% increase nationally in Covid-19 cases in
August. And now, in North Carolina, hospitalization rates are the
highest since July. This meeting will provide a space to share
concerns and experiences and to exchange ideas, and we will hear brief
reports from the working groups (Strategy, Finance, Governance) that
emerged from our open meetings this summer.</p>
<p>This fall the groups have developed a detailed analysis of UNC&#39;s
budgets and governance, titled “Another UNC is Possible.” A summary
statement will be discussed at the meeting.</p>
<p>UNC’s financial crisis did not begin with Covid-19, and now that we&#39;re
facing economic losses as a result of the pandemic, new approaches—to
the Spring semester and beyond—are needed.</p>
<p>Please distribute widely. All UNC students, employees, and community
neighbors are welcome.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNC-CH AAUP statement against changes to chancellor searches]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2020-09-16</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2020-09-16"/>
        <updated>2020-09-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The officers of the UNC-Chapel Hill Chapter of the American
Association of University Professors (AAUP) strongly condemn an
unprecedented policy revision that will be proposed to the Board of
Governors of the University of North Carolina this Thursday, September
17, 2020.</p>
<p>See the full <a href="/chancellor-searches">UNC-CH AAUP statement against changes to chancellor searches</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AAUP/UNC workers meeting 8/21 12PM]]></title>
        <id>https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2020-08-19</id>
        <link href="https://unc-ch-aaup.org/news#2020-08-19"/>
        <updated>2020-08-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As of August 17, 279 students and 45 employees at UNC-CH had tested positive, according to UNC-CH Campus Health (a rate of over 12%). Many of us were, therefore, relieved by yesterday&#39;s announcement that all undergraduate instruction at UNC-Chapel Hill would move on-line starting today, August 19.</p>
<p>But we are not out of the woods yet. Our leaders are making no move to send students home and have no plans to close the dorms. There will be no effort to reduce density at fraternities and sororities, over which the university has limited jurisdiction. In short, the threat of continued viral spread will remain high. Campus workers, the entire communities of Chapel Hill and Carrboro, as well as many students are still vulnerable.</p>
<p>The situation at other UNC campuses, forced by the BOG to stay open, is likely to get just as bad or worse. Clusters have already appeared at ECU, Appalachian State, NC State, and UNC-Wilmington.</p>
<p>In light of these conditions, we are asking you once again to join us in a call on our leaders to intervene. We have prepared a letter to Governor Cooper and other state leaders asking them to order all system campuses to close their dorms to all but the students who must stay on campus and to move instruction on-line. Simply fill out the form at the link below.</p>
<p>Click here to <a href="http://bit.ly/dysfUNCtional">read and send a letter</a> urging Governor Cooper and state and county health directors to close campus residences to most students and move all system instruction online.</p>
<p>We are also calling another meeting of faculty, staff, and students from UNC-CH and from other UNC campuses to discuss the situation and our next steps.</p>
<p>Please join us at the link below on Friday, August 21 at 12 noon ET.</p>
<p><a href="https://unc.zoom.us/j/94358093237">https://unc.zoom.us/j/94358093237</a></p>
<p>For the Zoom password, please email <a href="mailto:&#105;&#110;&#x66;&#111;&#64;&#x75;&#110;&#99;&#45;&#x63;&#x68;&#x2d;&#97;&#x61;&#x75;&#x70;&#46;&#x6f;&#x72;&#103;">&#105;&#110;&#x66;&#111;&#64;&#x75;&#110;&#99;&#45;&#x63;&#x68;&#x2d;&#97;&#x61;&#x75;&#x70;&#46;&#x6f;&#x72;&#103;</a> or DM <a href="https://twitter.com/unc_ch_aaup">@unc_ch_aaup</a>, or contact one of the officers below.</p>
<p>Please reach out to one of the AAUP officers with questions, etc.</p>
<p>Karen Booth  <a href="mailto:&#x6b;&#x61;&#x72;&#x65;&#110;&#x6d;&#x62;&#x6f;&#111;&#116;&#104;&#64;&#103;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#108;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#109;">&#x6b;&#x61;&#x72;&#x65;&#110;&#x6d;&#x62;&#x6f;&#111;&#116;&#104;&#64;&#103;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#108;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#109;</a></p>
<p>Michael Palm  <a href="mailto:&#x6d;&#119;&#x70;&#97;&#x6c;&#109;&#x40;&#x67;&#x6d;&#97;&#105;&#108;&#x2e;&#x63;&#111;&#109;">&#x6d;&#119;&#x70;&#97;&#x6c;&#109;&#x40;&#x67;&#x6d;&#97;&#105;&#108;&#x2e;&#x63;&#111;&#109;</a></p>
<p>Jay Smith  <a href="mailto:&#106;&#97;&#121;&#115;&#x6d;&#x69;&#116;&#x68;&#55;&#x31;&#x31;&#x40;&#103;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#108;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;">&#106;&#97;&#121;&#115;&#x6d;&#x69;&#116;&#x68;&#55;&#x31;&#x31;&#x40;&#103;&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#108;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;</a> </p>
<p>We hope to see you there! </p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>